azarticles.com 2008-06-17

# AZArticles - Privacy Policy

AZArticles.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for AZArticles.com.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.

 **Cookies**

Our Site uses cookies to keep our content organised in specific areas of our site, cookies may also be used to display ads and help keep those ads up to date.

 **Advertisers**

We occassionally use an outside ad company to display ads on our site, These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads may be collected by that outside ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

 **Registration Forms**

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name andemail).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to send information about our company, and to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Demographic and profile data may also be collected at our site.

We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

 **External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. AZArticles.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These security measures include password protected directories through the use of .htaccess files and customized cgi programs to prevent access to specific areas of the web site.

 **Children's Guidelines**

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:

1\. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.

2\. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent

3\. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:

> 1\. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.
> 
> 2\. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.
> 
> 3\. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity. 
> 
> 4\. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.
> 
> 5\. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.
> 
> 6\. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children.
> 
> 7\. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us.

1\. You can send email to [admin@millenniumonlinemarketing.com](mailto:admin@millenniumonlinemarketing.com)

 **Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or about your dealing with this website in general please send us an email: [admin@millenniumonlinemarketing.com](mailto:admin@millenniumonlinemarketing.com)
